A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, National Commission on Water Quality, Series 9 FA379
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Industries - Comments from Outside Groups: Procedure and Index (Box 12, Folder 487)
- Industries - Domestic Council Task Force Report, October 1975 (Box 12, Folder 488)
- Industries - Dr. Gee: Caption Summaries on Contract (Box 12, Folder 489)
- Industries - Iron and Steel - McKee - Comments (Box 12, Folder 490)
- Industries - Organic Chemicals - Catalytic - Comments (Box 12, Folder 491)
- Industries - Inorganic Chemicals - Catalytic - Comments (Box 12, Folder 492)
- Industries - Petroleum Refining - Engineering Science - Comments (Box 12, Folder 493)
- Industries - Pulp and Paper - Hazen and Sawyer - Comments (Box 12, Folder 494)
- Industries - Electroplating - Metal Finishing - Lancy - Comments (Box 12, Folder 495)
- Industries - Metal Finishing - Assessment of NBER Report (H. Cook paper April 9, 1975) (Box 12, Folder 496)
- Industries - Canned & Preserved Fruits & Vegetables - Environmental Associates - Comments (Box 12, Folder 497)
- Industries - Technology - Procon - (Plastics and Synthetics) - Comments on Draft Reports (Box 12, Folder 498)
- Industries - Textiles - Lockwood Green - Comments (Box 12, Folder 499)
- Industries - Steam Electric Power (Technology) - Teknekron - Comments (Box 12, Folder 500)
- Industries - Technology: Water Purification - Innovative Technologies - Comments on Draft Reports (Box 12, Folder 501)
- Industries - Technology: American Public Works - Needs Survey - Comments on Draft Reports (Box 12, Folder 502)
- Industries - Technology: Metcalf and Eddy - (Publicly Owned Treatment Works) - Comments on Draft Reports (Box 12, Folder 503)
- Industries - Urban Runoff - Black, Crow & Eidsness - Comments (Box 12, Folder 504)
- Industries - Construction Grants - Institutional - Touche Ross - Comments (Box 12, Folder 505)
- Industries - Enforcement - Institutional Environmental Law Institute - Comments (Box 12, Folder 506)
- Industries - Permit Program - Institutional - Energy & Environmental Analysis - Comments (Box 12, Folder 507)
- Industries - Permit Program - Contract Report Assessment (H. Cook paper July 17, 1975) (Box 12, Folder 508)
- Industries - Public Participation - Institutional - James Ragan Associates - Comments (Box 12, Folder 509)
- Industries - Regional: ABT Associates (Merrimack-Nashua) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 510)
- Industries - Regional: Stevens, Thompson & Runyan (Puget Sound) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 511)
- Industries - Regional: Houston Ship Channel (Box 12, Folder 512)
- Industries - Regional: Betz Environmental Engineers (Delaware River Basin) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 513)
- Industries - Regional: Stevens, Thompson & Runyan (Yellowstone) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 514)
- Industries - Regional: Dalton, Dalton, Little & Newport (Lake Erie) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 515)
- Industries - Lake Erie - Contractor Report Assessment (H. Cook paper June 14, 1975) (Box 12, Folder 516)
- Industries - Economics: Public Research Institute (Limitations on Foreign Trade) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 517)
- Industries - Economics: NBER (Pulp and Paper) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 518)
- Industries - Economics: DPRA (Feedlots) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 519)
- Industries - Economics: Battelle Memorial (Increased Swimming) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 520)
- Industries - Economics: Florida State University (Commercial Fisheries) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 521)
- Industries - Economics: Meta Systems (Municipal Options) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 522)
- Industries - Economics: The Conference Board (5 Pilot Studies) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 523)
- Industries - General Industry Studies: Battelle Memorial (Categories 1-38) - Comments on Draft Contractor Reports (Number One) (Box 13, Folder 524)
- Industries - General Industry Studies: Battelle Memorial (Categories 1-38) - Comments on Draft Contractor Reports (Number Two) (Box 13, Folder 525)
- Industries - General Industry Studies: Battelle Memorial (Categories 1-38) - Comments on Draft Contractor Reports (Number Three) (Box 13, Folder 526)
- Industries - Outside Groups - New York State (Box 13, Folder 527)
  Response to NAR letters to industry, states, cities and environmental groups.
- Industries - NAR Letter December 13, 1974 with Digest of Responses (Box 13, Folder 528)
- Industries - Industry - Associated Industries of Alabama (Box 13, Folder 529)
- Industries - Industry Comments: Canned Food & Vegetable Processing, NAR Letter December 13, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 530)
- Industry Comments - Chambers of Commerce (Box 13, Folder 531)
- Industry Comments - Chemical Processes (Box 13, Folder 532)
- Industry Comments - Dairy Products (Box 13, Folder 533)
- Industry Comments - Electroplating (Box 13, Folder 534)
- Industry Comments - Fertilizers (Box 13, Folder 535)
- Industry Comments - Forestry & Timber Products (Box 13, Folder 536)
- Industry Comments - Glass Manufacturing (Box 13, Folder 537)
- Industry Comments - Iron & Steel (Box 13, Folder 538)
- Industry Comments - Meats & Poultry (Box 13, Folder 539)
- Industry Comments - Mining (Box 13, Folder 540)
- Industry Comments - Miscellaneous Industries (Box 13, Folder 541)
- Industry Comments - Nonferrous Metals (Box 13, Folder 542)
- Industry Comments - Petroleum (Box 13, Folder 543)
- Industry Comments - Pulp & Paper (Box 13, Folder 544)
- Industry Comments - Rubber (Box 13, Folder 545)
- Industry Comments - Steam Electric Power (Box 13, Folder 546)
- Industry Comments - Textiles (Box 13, Folder 547)
- Industry Comments - Transportation (Box 13, Folder 548)
- Industry Comments - Water Conditioning (Box 13, Folder 549)
- Industry Comments - NAR Letter October 24, 1974, with Digest of Responses (Box 13, Folder 550)
- Industry Comments - Governors' Responses to NAR Letter of October 24, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 551)
- Industry Comments - Cities: NAR Letter, 3rd Week of August 1974, with Digest of Comments Received (Box 13, Folder 552)
- Industry Comments - Cities: Responses to NAR Letter, August 1974 (Box 13, Folder 553)
- Industry Comments - Environmentalists: NAR Letter of April 7, 1974 with Digest Highlights (Box 13, Folder 554)
- Industry Comments - Environmentalists' Responses to NAR Letter, April 7, 1974 (1) (Box 13, Folder 555)
- Industry Comments - Environmentalists' Responses to NAR Letter, April 7, 1974 (2) (Box 13, Folder 556)
- Industry Comments - Environmentalists' Responses to NAR Letter, April 7, 1974 (3) (Box 14, Folder 557)
- Industry Comments - Environmentalists' Responses to NAR Letter, April 7, 1974 (4) (Box 14, Folder 558)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Outlines, November 9, 1973 - June 17, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 559)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Preamble - May 8, 1975 Through Final Report (Box 14, Folder 560)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Background - July 31, 1974 Through First Staff Draft (Box 14, Folder 561)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Background, September 2, 1975 - December 31, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 562)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - First Staff Draft - Public Release / Participation, September 2, 1975 - December 31, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 563)
- Reports - "Opinions" Paper of Program Staff/Commission by Joe Moore, July 31, 1975 and August 8, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 564)
  i.e., staff conclusions
- Reports - Procedure for Completion (Box 14, Folder 565)
- Reports - Recommendations / Options / Issues Papers Prepared by Clarke, September 8, 1975 - December 3, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 566)
  One paper by Moore
- Reports - Chapter I: Issues and Findings - Drafts (1), September 9, 1975-November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 567)
  Originally called "Synthesis" and "Discussion Document."
- Reports - Chapter I: Issues and Findings - Drafts (2), September 9, 1975-November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 568)
- Reports - Chapter I: Issues and Findings - Drafts (3), September 9, 1975-November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 569)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Benefits & Health Controversy (Box 14, Folder 570)
- Reports - Costs of Treatment / Capital Requirements (Box 14, Folder 571)
- Reports - Cook Paper, "Major Questions", October 10, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 572)
- Reports - Cook Paper, "National Water Commission Experience", November 6, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 573)
- Reports - Cook Paper, "Catch-up Period", February 18, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 574)
- Reports - Cook Paper, "Report: Proposed Format" (Box 14, Folder 575)
  Used as basis for Chairman's "Separate Views" in Commission Report.
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafting Through First Staff Draft of September 2, 1975 (General) (Box 14, Folder 576)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Technology - (Staff Drafts to September 2, 1975) (General) (Box 14, Folder 577)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Tech/Industrial - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (Box 14, Folder 578)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Tech/Municipal - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (Box 14, Folder 579)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Tech/Agricultural - Non-point & Innovative (Box 14, Folder 580)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Economic & Social - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (1) (Box 15, Folder 581)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Economic & Social - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (2) (Box 15, Folder 582)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Environmental - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (1) (Box 15, Folder 583)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Environmental - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (2) (Box 15, Folder 584)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Institutional - (Staff Drafts Up to September 15, 1975) (1) (Box 15, Folder 585)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Institutional - (Staff Drafts Up to September 15, 1975) (2) (Box 15, Folder 586)
- Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Regional- (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (Box 15, Folder 587)
- Reports - First Staff Draft - "Partial"; Preliminary 1 of 3: Technology Chapter, September 2, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 588)
- Reports - First Staff Draft - "Partial"; Preliminary 2 of 3: Economic Impacts, September 2, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 589)
- Reports - First Staff Draft - "Partial"; Preliminary 3 of 3: Regional, Institutional, & Environmental, September 2, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 590)
- Reports - First Staff Draft - Comments from Outside Groups, September 2, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 591)
- Reports - Outside Comments - First Staff Draft - Overall (1) (Box 15, Folder 592)
- Reports - Outside Comments - First Staff Draft - Overall (2) (Box 15, Folder 593)
- Reports - Outside Comments - First Staff Draft - Technology (Box 15, Folder 594)
- Reports - Outside Comments - First Staff Draft - Economic (Box 15, Folder 595)
- Reports - Outside Comments - First Staff Draft - Environmental (Box 15, Folder 596)
- Reports - Outside Comments - First Staff Draft - Institutional (Box 15, Folder 597)
- Reports - Outside Comments - First Staff Draft - Regional (Box 15, Folder 598)
- Reports - Domestic Council Task Force - Genesis & Establishment (Box 15, Folder 599)
- Reports - Domestic Council Task Force - Two "Pilot" Studies: "Pulp and Paper," and "Electroplating" (Box 15, Folder 600)
- Reports - Domestic Council Task Force - Organization and Development of Report (Box 16, Folder 601)
- Reports - Domestic Council Task Force - Draft Reports, September 8 and October 3, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 602)
- Reports - Domestic Council Task Force - Report, October 6, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 603)
- Reports - Domestic Council Task Force - Aftermath of Report (Box 16, Folder 604)
- Reports - Task Force - NCWQ Review (Box 16, Folder 605)
- Reports - Second Staff Draft - (General), October 10, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 606)
- Reports - Second Staff Draft - Chapter I: Issues & Findings 10/17/75 (1 of 3), October 10, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 607)
- Reports - Second Staff Draft - Chapter II, III: Technology and Economic (2 of 3), October 10, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 608)
- Reports - Second Staff Draft - Chapter IV, V, & VI: Environmental; Institutional; Regional (3 of 3), October 10, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 609)
- Comments From Outside Groups (including Dr. Gee) (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 610)
- Comments From Outside Groups (including Dr. Gee) (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 611)
- Third Staff Draft - General, November 18, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 612)
- Third Staff Draft - Chapter I: Issues and Findings, November 18, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 613)
- Third Staff Draft - Chapter II and III: Technology and Economic (1 of 2), November 18, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 614)
- Third Staff Draft - Chapter II and III: Technology and Economic (2 of 2), November 18, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 615)
- Third Staff Draft - Chapter IV, V & VI & Appendix: Environmental; Institutional; Regional (1 of 2), November 18, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 616)
- Third Staff Draft - Chapter IV, V & VI & Appendix: Environmental; Institutional; Regional (2 of 2), November 18, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 617)
- Final Staff Report to Commission, April 1976 (Box 16, Folder 618)
  See Box 1 for copy
- Staff, Technical Backup Documents to Staff Report (Box 16, Folder 619)
  See Box 1 for reports
- Final Contractor Reports (Box 16, Folder 620)
- Third Staff Draft, Dr. Gee's Comments (Box 16, Folder 621)
- Third Staff Draft - Outside Comments: Executive Branch, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 622)
  See also January hearings.
- Third Staff Draft - Outside Comments: Agriculture, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 623)
- Third Staff Draft - Outside Comments: Cities & Counties (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 624)
  See also January 1976 hearings.
- Third Staff Draft - Outside Comments: Cities & Counties (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 625)
- Third Staff Draft - Outside Comments: States and State Organizations, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 626)
- Third Staff Draft - Outside Comments: Industry (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 627)
- Third Staff Draft - Outside Comments: Industry (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 628)
- Third Staff Draft - Outside Comments: Environmentalists, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 629)
- Third Staff Draft - Outside Comments: Private Firms & Citizens, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 630)
- Hearings - Transcript: San Francisco, January 10, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 631)
- Hearings - Transcript, Attachment "A": San Francisco, January 10, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 632)
- Hearings - Transcript: Chicago, January 10, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 633)
- Hearings - Transcript: Fort Worth, January 12, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 634)
- Hearings - Transcript: Boston, January 12, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 635)
- Hearings - Transcript: Washington, DC (first day), January 19, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 636)
  NAR chaired
- Hearings - Transcript: Washington, DC (second day), January 20, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 637)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft - Overall (Policies) (Box 17, Folder 638)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: San Francisco (1 of 2), January 10, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 639)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: San Francisco (2 of 2), January 10, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 640)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: Chicago, January 10, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 641)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: Fort Worth, January 12, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 642)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: Boston, January 12, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 643)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: Washington, DC (first day) (1 of 3), January 19, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 644)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: Washington, DC (first day) (2 of 3), January 19, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 645)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: Washington, DC (first day) (3 of 3), January 19, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 646)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: Washington, DC (second day) (1 of 2), January 20, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 647)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: Washington, DC (second day) (2 of 2), January 20, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 648)
- Hearings - Third Staff Draft: Washington, DC - Policies, January 19 and 20, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 649)
- Hearings - History of Development of Recommendations, January-October, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 650)
- Hearings - Recommendations: Outside Groups (from First Draft September 1975, through January 1976 Hearings), 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 651)
- Commission - Agenda and Recommendations - February 17, 1976 Meeting (Box 18, Folder 652)
- Commission - Comments on February 17 Recommendations (Box 18, Folder 653)
- Commission - Development of Recommendations - February 18 and 19, 1976 Meeting (Box 18, Folder 654)
- Commission - Agenda and Recommendations - February 19, 1976 Meeting (Box 18, Folder 655)
- Commission - Development of Recommendations February 18 through February 19, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 656)
- Commission - Development of Recommendations February 20 through February 27, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 657)
- Commission - Development of Recommendations February 25 through March 2, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 658)
- Commission - Agenda and Recommendations - March 2, 1976 Meeting (Box 18, Folder 659)
- Commission - Transmittal Letter March 18, 1976 (Data February 24 - March 18, 1976) (Box 18, Folder 660)
- Commission - Individual Views of Commissioners (Box 19, Folder 661)
- Commission - Individual Views of Chairman (Box 19, Folder 662)
- Commission - Text (with Individual Views) (Prior to Printing), March 18, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 663)
- Commission - Press Releases, News Items, Status, and Comments on Report (Box 19, Folder 664)
- Commission - NCWQ Staff Discussion of Commission at Seminar of Water Pollution Control Federation, April 6, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 665)
- Commission - Staff (final): Printing & Distribution (Box 19, Folder 666)
  See also Budget & Commission report files
- Commission - Printing & Distribution & Costs, March 18, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 667)
- Distribution - Mailing Lists, March 18, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 668)
- Distribution - Telephone / Letter Requests (Box 19, Folder 669)
- Distribution - NCWQ - 2 (Box 19, Folder 670)
- Distribution - Advisory Committee for the Permits Program (Box 19, Folder 671)
- Distribution - Advisory Committee on Public Participation (Box 19, Folder 672)
- Distribution - Association of Metropolitan Sewerage Agencies (Box 19, Folder 673)
- Distribution - Chamber of Commerce (Box 19, Folder 674)
- Distribution - Commission Members (Box 19, Folder 675)
- Distribution - Commission Staff (Box 19, Folder 676)
- Distribution - Committee of Consultants on Irrigated Agriculture (Box 19, Folder 677)
- Distribution - Consultants (Box 19, Folder 678)
- Distribution - Electric Companies (Box 19, Folder 679)
- Distribution - Environmentalists (Box 19, Folder 680)
- Distribution - General Mailing (Box 19, Folder 681)
- Distribution - Governors (Box 19, Folder 682)
- Distribution - Industry Trade Associations (Box 19, Folder 683)
- Distribution - Institute of Ecology Advisory Committee (Box 19, Folder 684)
- Distribution - Legal Study (Box 19, Folder 685)
- Distribution - Magazines (Box 19, Folder 686)
- Distribution - National Academy of Sciences Advisory Committee (Box 19, Folder 687)
- Distribution - NRC (Box 19, Folder 688)
- Distribution - Regional Advisory Groups (Box 19, Folder 689)
- Distribution - Senate and House (Box 19, Folder 690)
- Distribution - Trade Press (Box 19, Folder 691)
- Distribution - Water Pollution Control Federation (Box 19, Folder 692)
- Distribution - Witnesses (Hearings) (Box 19, Folder 693)
- Distribution - 208 Program (Box 19, Folder 694)
- Distribution - Paul Clark's Lists (Box 19, Folder 695)
- Distribution - J.C. (Prolman) (Box 19, Folder 696)
- Distribution - Chicago Meeting (Box 19, Folder 697)
- Distribution - Kansas City Meeting (Box 19, Folder 698)
- Distribution - Portland Meeting (Box 19, Folder 699)
- Distribution - 10 C (Box 19, Folder 700)
- Distribution - 11 C (Box 19, Folder 701)
- Distribution - 20 AP (Box 19, Folder 702)
- Distribution - Commission Report: Promotion, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 703)
- Books - Council on Environmental Quality - "Environmental Quality - The First Annual Report of the Council on Environmental Quality", August 1970 (Box 19, Folder 0703A)
- Books - Council on Environmental Quality - "Environmental Quality - The Sixth Annual Report", 1975 (Box 19, Folder 0703B)
- Books - Council on Environmental Quality - "Environmental Quality - The Seventh Annual Report", 1976 (Box 19, Folder 0703C)
- Hearings, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 703)
  Water Pollution Control Legislation - 1971 Hearings (NAR testimony, pages 477-509) Agriculture - Environmental and Consumer Protection Appropriations for 1974 Hearings
- Hearings, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 0703E)
  Agriculture - Environmental and Consumer Protection Appropriations for 1975 Hearings (NAR testimony pages 1-34) Implementation of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1974 Hearings
- Hearings, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 703)
  Implementation of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act, May 1975 Hearings Implementation of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act, February 1976 Hearings
- Legislative History - History of the Water Pollution Control Act, Amendments of 1972, Volumes 1 and II, January 1973 (Box 20, Folder 0703G)
- Legislative History, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 0703H)
  Institutions for Effective Management of the Environment, Part I January 1970 New Directions in U.S. Water Policy: Summary, Conclusions and Recommendations from the Final Report of the National Water Commission, June 1973
- Legislative History - The Act - Public Law 92-500 (Amendments to the Federal Water Pollution Control Act), October 18, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 704)
- Legislative History - The Act: Water Pollution Laws (Box 20, Folder 705)
- Legislative History - Citizens Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality - Reports (Box 20, Folder 706)
- Legislative History - General Accounting Office Report, November 1969 (Box 20, Folder 707)
- Legislative History - General Accounting Office Reports (Box 20, Folder 708)
- Legislative History - Research & Development (General Accounting Office Report), January 16, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 709)
- Legislative History - General Accounting Office Report - "Implementation of PL500 is Slow", December 1974 (Box 20, Folder 710)
- Legislative History - General Accounting Office Report (Reducing Waste Treatment Plant Costs), May 8, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 711)
- Legislative History - Research & Development (Box 20, Folder 712)
  See also General Accounting Office (GAO) and Water Pollution Control Foundation (WPCF) reports
- Legislative History - Environmental Policy: An Annotated Bibliography - State University of New York, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 713)
- Legislative History - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) - Annual Report, mid-1975 (Box 20, Folder 714)
- Donna Mitchell Reports - To New York State Federal Legislation, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 715)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (A-D), 1960 (Box 20, Folder 716)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (E-H), 1960 (Box 20, Folder 717)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (H-S), 1960 (Box 20, Folder 718)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (T-Z), 1960 (Box 20, Folder 719)
- Donna Mitchell Reports - Cover Memo, (A-Ai), 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 720)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (Aj-C), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 721)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (D-He), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 722)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (Hi-N), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 723)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (O-Ta), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 724)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (Tr-Y), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 725)
- Donna Mitchell Reports - Cover Letter, Index, (A-Ba), 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 726)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (Bu-D), 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 727)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (E-N), 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 728)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (P-Z), 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 729)
- Donna Mitchell Reports - Cover Memo, Index, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 730)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (A-B), 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 731)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (C-D), 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 732)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (E-L), 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 733)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (M-R), 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 734)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (S-Z), 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 735)
- Donna Mitchell Reports - Cover Memo, Index, (A-Co), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 736)